



Ferhat Adıbelli

• Address: Gazeteci Hasan Tahsin Cad., No:77, Karabağlar, 35150, İzmir, Turkey

Website: https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferhatadibelli9/

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/19093788/ferhat-adibelli

Github: https://github.com/FerhatAdibelli0

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 15/11/1991 **Nationality:** Turkish

ABOUT ME

I'm Ferhat. I am from Turkey, I live in Turkey. As a FullStack Developer, I`m very passionate and talented about **ReactJS**, **NextJS**, **NodeJS**, **ExpressJS**, **MongoDB**, **and MySQL**. I devoted myself to learning, implementing, adapting, and creating throughout my life to build intelligent web apps to help people and improve life quality around the world. As a Web Developer with 14 months of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[02/2022 - 05/2022] **Frontend Developer**

Alme Tech

Country: Turkey

Main activities and responsibilities:

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components Writing some end-to-end test on JestJS

[01/2021 - 01/2022] **Freelancer**

Upwork

Country: Turkey

Main activities and responsibilities:

Upwork helped me find my first job as a FullStack Developer. It allows me to focus on what is most important for my clients - product and project development.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[2010 - 2014] Bachelor of Science

Turkish Military Academy - Ankara

Field(s) of study: Industrial and Systems Engineering

Final grade: 3.65/4

[2020 - Current] Master's degree (Thesis)

Gazi Univercity - Ankara

Field(s) of study: Computer Forensic

DIGITAL SKILLS

Very good at programming in: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Boostrap, Jquery, Javascript | React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript | Backend: NodeJS, Express, socket.io | RESTful api | Git | Github | graphQL | DenoJs | nextjs | Agile (Scrum) | Postman | FireBase | Heroku Cloud | Web Socket | Unit Testing | Sequelize and Mongoose | Object-Oriented Programming | MongoDB, MySQL | JIRa

HONOURS AND AWARDS

ReactJS -- The Complete Guide Awarding institution: Academind https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UPC_WHLoWUOf9ADO-6JEahHS7nlzeJb0/view?usp=sharing

ReactJS -- Web Programming Awarding institution: BTK Academy https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GIUX8brBrknCW8iVHf1Wg_CLPz_g7vMr/view?usp=sharing

NodeJS -- The Complete Guide Awarding institution: Academind https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QxMxt8Wh-j9NF83Sqqsbr8l3E6rRcaqK/view?usp=sharing

Git & Github -- Version Control System Awarding institution: BTK Academy https://drive.google.com/file/d/17g_fC7fDGiHUKurpCb3R6_6AxzE91zq4/view?usp=sharing

Language Competency Awarding institution: American Culture School https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HOzdEH-8ytlH_u9XtqXbyaSJIGwNmwDa/view?usp=sharing